<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EditionCrafter Hugo Project</title><link>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/</link><description>Recent content on EditionCrafter Hugo Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023, Columbia University</copyright><atom:link href="https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/introduction/</guid><description>Collecting Medical Knowledge Across Generations Historians of science agree that something pivotal happened in England in the latter decades of the sixteenth century, as medieval theories about the body or the natural world diminished in the face of new discoveries, new ideas, and a new experimental method. And yet, the reading habits of sixteenth-century English artisans, bureaucrats, merchants, and farmers tell a different story, one that this project seeks to explore.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/about/</guid><description>About As of May 2024, this website features preliminary transcriptions of the first few folios of Trinity College Cambridge MS O.8.35, a mid-fifteenth century Middle English medical manuscript that was owned by Henry Dyngley (ca. 1515–1589). These transcriptions were prepared from a digital facsimile created by the librarians at Trinity College. Transcriptions and high-res images of the manuscript are viewable on the folios pages. To read about Henry Dyngley and this manuscript as part of his collection, visit the Introduction page.</description></item><item><title>Folios</title><link>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/folios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/folios/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cu-mkp.github.io/dyngleyfamily-editioncrafter-website/credits/</guid><description>Transcriptions and Annotations Transcriptions: Melissa Reynolds, Mellon Postdoctoral Fellow, Wolf Humanities Center, University of Pennsylvania; mbreyn(at)sas.upenn.edu
Digital Facsimile: High-res images provided by the librarians at the Wren Library, Trinity College Cambridge in IIIF Format; IIIF Manifest
EditionCrafter Platform Development Lead Developer: Nicholas Laiacona, Performant Software Solutions
Making and Knowing Team: Pamela H. Smith, Seth Low Professor of History, Columbia University
Naomi Rosenkranz, Associate Director of the Center for Science and Society, Columbia University</description></item></channel></rss>